home here in Washington after the long
trails you the long journey you've had.
>> Um, it's always one day at a time for
me. You know, my journey in in the
league, you know, it's been uh
it's been a little rocky, but you know,
I use that for fuel. And it's I'm always
I'm always trying to prove I'm always
trying to prove it to myself. I'm always
trying to prove it to my teammates and
coaches, you know, that I belong in this
league. and uh wherever I can get in, I
want to fit in and continue to try and
make any team I'm on um a contender and
just go out there and play the best I
can.
>> What do you feel you've been able to
show them, they keep you back?
>> Uh just just a dog, you know, when I go
on the field, I just feel like I'm a
dog. Like whatever needs to be done, you
know, that's what I go out there for.
Highly competitive. Um I just want to
win. a good teammate and then uh you
know just relentless you know just
when when
you know for 60 minutes I'm I'm I'm
going to leave it all out there every
single Sunday whatever whenever we play
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, whatever you
know I just I just love this game so
much and um you know I just continuously
want to show my passion.
>> Nikki,
>> hi Jeremy. Um just generally what are
your expectations um with David Blau
taking over the offense?
>> Um expect him to, you know, be
explosive, run the ball, pass the ball,
play action. Um be unique, creative.
He's a he's a great mind. Uh he didn't
get this job for for no reason. And for
him to be so young and talented, and uh
you know, everybody wanted everybody
wanted him. So we're lucky to have him.
And I'm just so excited to see his
creativity. And uh also, you know, our
other uh coaches on the staff as well.
They they got creative minds and you
know, we have former offensive
coordinators and and head coaches that
are going to be able to put their input
in and going to be able to have this
this um this offense rocking this year.
>> And then with um Jerome Form Ford and
Rashad White joining the room, I mean,
how much how much do you know about
them? Did you know them personally at
all before they they came here?
>> Uh I haven't I didn't know them
personally, but uh I I know who they
are. uh you know, just playing the
position. You kind of watch everybody
throughout the league and you you know,
you hear the names and you go for the
position. So, uh I heard of those guys.
They've had great careers and I'm
excited for them to be in the room.
Excited for to see what they bring to
the table this year and um in our
football team.
>> Donna,
>> hey Jeremy, welcome back. Uh you talked
about always having to show them what
you could do. What do you feel that
you've grown over time the most as you
come back to the Commanders this year?
>> Uh, you know, I was just thinking about
that, you know, going into year 10, I
was just reminiscing over my career, you
know, from my rookie year to now, how
much I've learned and how much I grown.
And, um, I think the one thing I could
take from it is just never give up, you
know, um, believe in yourself. And
that's what I continue to to do. and you
know continue to have faith that I am I
belong here and that um you know my work
ethic is going to show no matter what
and I'm going to be a good teammate and
continue to just come to work and when
and for the 60 minutes just play with
like you know just be a dog out there
and just fight to win you know the
league is is it's so tough to win it
comes down to two or three plays you
know how can we turn those two and three
plays on our side to win every single
week and uh just knowing the details
every single week going into it, just
having a high IQ of football and uh
loving this game, you know, playing with
passion and I think that's what I
continuously show and have grown into in
my career from year one to going into my
10th season. Um just knowing what to
expect. um being prepared for every
single moment. You know, throughout my
career, I've been able to have reps in
every single moment. Um in practice as
well as in games when the bullets are
flying. So, no moment is too big for me
and I use that to my advantage and just
being able to play fast.
>> And what psyches you most about being
back here this year with a lot of new
faces that's going to be in this offense
this year? Um, I I'm excited to see what
everybody brings. You know, it's it's
it's new. It's it's it's exciting. Um,
you know, I've been on both sides of the
coin so far since I' I've been here. You
know, we we went all the way it was one
game away from the Super Bowl and then,
uh, you know, last year just just didn't
go our way. Um, so I know for sure we
coming with a a whole different mindset.
I know the guys that's that's coming
through the building knows what to
expect as well. you know, with AP and DQ
and those guys that that work hard,
you know, they bringing in the right
guys, you know, and,
you know, just being able to meet my new
I'm excited to meet my new team my new
teammates and, you know, create new
memories with them throughout the, you
know, offseason and going into camp and
continue to put work in um to be our
very best and give us the best chance to
win.
>> Congratulations again of being back.
>> Thank you, Ben.
Hey Jeremy, uh, welcome back. Um, since
my colleagues I think got a lot of the
questions about you, I want to ask you
about one of your teammates. Uh, what do
you think's the next step for Bill going
into his second season? I always say,
man, Bill's sky's is the limit for Bill,
but um you know, Bill works his tail off
and the you know, the more that he works
his tail off and the more that he puts
in the work and the film study and he
continues to grow and he continues to
mature um you know, throughout the
football and you know, continues to
learn how to be a pro. I mean, the sky's
is the limit for the for for Bill and
I'm so excited to be able to be a small
part of his career, be a small part of
his life, and uh, you know, continue to
watch him throughout his career, you
know, and wherever he wants to take it,
he could take it, you know. Um, I put no
no floor, no ceiling on him. like, you
know, I I see I see him being being the
very best he can and even even last year
when he first came in and being a rookie
till the end of the season, it was so
much growth, you know, and I'm just
excited to see him go through a whole
off season and um through OTAAS and grow
through OTAAS and have summer, grow
through fall camp and then have going
into year two.
And um obviously their expectation is
playing more under center versus almost
shotgun exclusively the last couple of
years. From a running back perspective,
what what change what does that mean for
you in terms of how you're going to see
the world?
>> Um you know, I've had experience in
both. You know, most of my career has
been under center. I have shotgun reps.
So it's it's whatever the system is and
we just going to execute what we need to
execute. Um, you know, being under
center gives you opportunity to have
more play action and run or pass. You
It's hard to tell with the defense and
the eyes and all those type of things.
And I'm pretty sure we're going to be in
shotgun as well. So, you know, I just
have trust in my my coaches and them
scheming things to be able to go out
there and execute and go out there and
win every single game.
>> Cool.
>> Thanks. And again, welcome back.
>> Appreciate you.
>> Cool. Thanks, Jimmy. Appreciate it.
>> All right.
>> Thanks. Thank you.